[
    {
        "display_question": "重庆",
        "answer_ok": ["重庆"],
        "display_answer": "重庆"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "全国",
        "answer_ok": ["全国"],
        "display_answer": "全国"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "大红桥",
        "answer_ok": ["大红桥"],
        "display_answer": "大红桥"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "张家湾",
        "answer_ok": ["张家湾"],
        "display_answer": "张家湾"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "齐化门",
        "answer_ok": ["齐化门"],
        "display_answer": "齐化门"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "德胜门",
        "answer_ok": ["德胜门"],
        "display_answer": "德胜门"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "昌平",
        "answer_ok": ["昌平"],
        "display_answer": "昌平"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "南口",
        "answer_ok": ["南口"],
        "display_answer": "南口"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "天津",
        "answer_ok": ["天津"],
        "display_answer": "天津"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "河南",
        "answer_ok": ["河南"],
        "display_answer": "河南"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "吉林",
        "answer_ok": ["吉林"],
        "display_answer": "吉林"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "苏州",
        "answer_ok": ["苏州"],
        "display_answer": "苏州"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "学校",
        "answer_ok": ["学校"],
        "display_answer": "学校"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "解散",
        "answer_ok": ["解散"],
        "display_answer": "解散"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "绍兴",
        "answer_ok": ["绍兴"],
        "display_answer": "绍兴"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "握手",
        "answer_ok": ["握手"],
        "display_answer": "握手"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "凤阳",
        "answer_ok": ["凤阳"],
        "display_answer": "凤阳"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "海贼",
        "answer_ok": ["海賊"],
        "display_answer": "海贼"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "安定",
        "answer_ok": ["安定"],
        "display_answer": "安定"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "柔道",
        "answer_ok": ["柔道"],
        "display_answer": "柔道"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "音乐",
        "answer_ok": ["音乐"],
        "display_answer": "音乐"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "章丘",
        "answer_ok": ["章丘"],
        "display_answer": "章丘"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "吴郡",
        "answer_ok": ["吴郡"],
        "display_answer": "吴郡"          
    }, 
    {
        "display_question": "宝坻",
        "answer_ok": ["宝坻"],
        "display_answer": "宝坻"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "定兴",
        "answer_ok": ["定兴"],
        "display_answer": "定兴"          
    },
    {
        "display_question": "沧州",
        "answer_ok": ["沧州"],
        "display_answer": "沧州"   
    },
    {
        "display_question": "吴桥",
        "answer_ok": ["吴桥"],
        "display_answer": "吴桥"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "宜兴",
        "answer_ok": ["宜兴"],
        "display_answer": "宜兴"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "武清",
        "answer_ok": ["武清"],
        "display_answer": "武清"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "杨村",
        "answer_ok": ["杨村"],
        "display_answer": "杨村"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "体育",
        "answer_ok": ["体育"],
        "display_answer": "体育"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "万寿山",
        "answer_ok": ["万寿山"],
        "display_answer": "万寿山"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "颐和园",
        "answer_ok": ["颐和园"],
        "display_answer": "颐和园"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "故宫",
        "answer_ok": ["故宫"],
        "display_answer": "故宫"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "关山",
        "answer_ok": ["关山"],
        "display_answer": "关山"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "卢沟",
        "answer_ok": ["卢沟"],
        "display_answer": "卢沟"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "金属",
        "answer_ok": ["金属"],
        "display_answer": "金属"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "浮桥",
        "answer_ok": ["浮桥"],
        "display_answer": "浮桥"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "禁止",
        "answer_ok": ["禁止"],
        "display_answer": "禁止"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "九河",
        "answer_ok": ["九河"],
        "display_answer": "九河"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "貂皮",
        "answer_ok": ["貂皮"],
        "display_answer": "貂皮"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "人参",
        "answer_ok": ["人参"],
        "display_answer": "人参"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "逃走",
        "answer_ok": ["逃走"],
        "display_answer": "逃走"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "必要",
        "answer_ok": ["必要"],
        "display_answer": "必要"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "保定府",
        "answer_ok": ["保定府"],
        "display_answer": "保定府"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "南京",
        "answer_ok": ["南京"],
        "display_answer": "南京"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "西藏",
        "answer_ok": ["西藏"],
        "display_answer": "西藏"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "新疆",
        "answer_ok": ["新疆"],
        "display_answer": "新疆"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "时间",
        "answer_ok": ["时间"],
        "display_answer": "时间"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "英国",
        "answer_ok": ["英国"],
        "display_answer": "英国"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "香水",
        "answer_ok": ["香水"],
        "display_answer": "香水"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "旅行",
        "answer_ok": ["旅行"],
        "display_answer": "旅行"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "电话",
        "answer_ok": ["电话"],
        "display_answer": "电话"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "歌手",
        "answer_ok": ["歌手"],
        "display_answer": "歌手"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "电车",
        "answer_ok": ["电车"],
        "display_answer": "电车"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "北海楼",
        "answer_ok": ["北海楼"],
        "display_answer": "北海楼"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "万寿宫",
        "answer_ok": ["万寿宫"],
        "display_answer": "万寿宫"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "北大关",
        "answer_ok": ["北大关"],
        "display_answer": "北大关"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "汉沟",
        "answer_ok": ["汉沟"],
        "display_answer": "汉沟"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "柴达木",
        "answer_ok": ["柴达木"],
        "display_answer": "柴达木"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "西安",
        "answer_ok": ["西安"],
        "display_answer": "西安"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "咸阳",
        "answer_ok": ["咸阳"],
        "display_answer": "咸阳"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "大豆",
        "answer_ok": ["大豆"],
        "display_answer": "大豆"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "延安",
        "answer_ok": ["延安"],
        "display_answer": "延安"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "陕西",
        "answer_ok": ["陕西"],
        "display_answer": "陕西"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "英语",
        "answer_ok": ["英语"],
        "display_answer": "英语"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "潼关",
        "answer_ok": ["潼关"],
        "display_answer": "潼关"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "汉口",
        "answer_ok": ["汉口"],
        "display_answer": "汉口"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "信阳",
        "answer_ok": ["信阳"],
        "display_answer": "信阳"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "驻马店",
        "answer_ok": ["驻马店"],
        "display_answer": "驻马店"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "横店",
        "answer_ok": ["横店"],
        "display_answer": "横店"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "衡阳",
        "answer_ok": ["衡阳"],
        "display_answer": "衡阳"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "湖南",
        "answer_ok": ["湖南"],
        "display_answer": "湖南"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "广西",
        "answer_ok": ["广西"],
        "display_answer": "广西"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "四川",
        "answer_ok": ["四川"],
        "display_answer": "四川"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "成都",
        "answer_ok": ["成都"],
        "display_answer": "成都"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "重庆",
        "answer_ok": ["重庆"],
        "display_answer": "重庆"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "贵州",
        "answer_ok": ["贵州"],
        "display_answer": "贵州"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "遵义",
        "answer_ok": ["遵义"],
        "display_answer": "遵义"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "贵阳",
        "answer_ok": ["贵阳"],
        "display_answer": "贵阳"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "云南",
        "answer_ok": ["云南"],
        "display_answer": "云南"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "昆明",
        "answer_ok": ["昆明"],
        "display_answer": "昆明"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "龙门",
        "answer_ok": ["龙门"],
        "display_answer": "龙门"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "黄河",
        "answer_ok": ["黄河"],
        "display_answer": "黄河"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "山西",
        "answer_ok": ["山西"],
        "display_answer": "山西"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "榆次",
        "answer_ok": ["榆次"],
        "display_answer": "榆次"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "太原",
        "answer_ok": ["太原"],
        "display_answer": "太原"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "寿阳",
        "answer_ok": ["寿阳"],
        "display_answer": "寿阳"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "河北",
        "answer_ok": ["河北"],
        "display_answer": "河北"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "石家庄",
        "answer_ok": ["石家庄"],
        "display_answer": "石家庄"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "保定",
        "answer_ok": ["保定"],
        "display_answer": "保定"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "沧州",
        "answer_ok": ["沧州"],
        "display_answer": "沧州"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "禹城",
        "answer_ok": ["禹城"],
        "display_answer": "禹城"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "山东",
        "answer_ok": ["山东"],
        "display_answer": "山东"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "济南",
        "answer_ok": ["济南"],
        "display_answer": "济南"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "曲阜",
        "answer_ok": ["曲阜"],
        "display_answer": "曲阜"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "兖州",
        "answer_ok": ["兖州"],
        "display_answer": "兖州"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "龙潭",
        "answer_ok": ["龙潭"],
        "display_answer": "龙潭"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "镇江",
        "answer_ok": ["镇江"],
        "display_answer": "镇江"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "昆山",
        "answer_ok": ["昆山"],
        "display_answer": "昆山"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "无锡",
        "answer_ok": ["无锡"],
        "display_answer": "无锡"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "苏州",
        "answer_ok": ["苏州"],
        "display_answer": "苏州"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "松江",
        "answer_ok": ["松江"],
        "display_answer": "松江"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "浙江",
        "answer_ok": ["浙江"],
        "display_answer": "浙江"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "金华",
        "answer_ok": ["金华"],
        "display_answer": "金华"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "瑞金",
        "answer_ok": ["瑞金"],
        "display_answer": "瑞金"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "江西",
        "answer_ok": ["江西"],
        "display_answer": "江西"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "福州",
        "answer_ok": ["福州"],
        "display_answer": "福州"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "泉州",
        "answer_ok": ["泉州"],
        "display_answer": "泉州"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "金门",
        "answer_ok": ["金门"],
        "display_answer": "金门"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "厦门",
        "answer_ok": ["厦门"],
        "display_answer": "厦门"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "广东",
        "answer_ok": ["广东"],
        "display_answer": "广东"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "海南",
        "answer_ok": ["海南"],
        "display_answer": "海南"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "九龙",
        "answer_ok": ["九龙"],
        "display_answer": "九龙"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "老挝",
        "answer_ok": ["老挝"],
        "display_answer": "老挝"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "泰国",
        "answer_ok": ["泰国"],
        "display_answer": "泰国"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "曼谷",
        "answer_ok": ["曼谷"],
        "display_answer": "曼谷"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "秘密",
        "answer_ok": ["秘密"],
        "display_answer": "秘密"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "缅甸",
        "answer_ok": ["缅甸"],
        "display_answer": "缅甸"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "印度",
        "answer_ok": ["印度"],
        "display_answer": "印度"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "南平",
        "answer_ok": ["南平"],
        "display_answer": "南平"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "延吉",
        "answer_ok": ["延吉"],
        "display_answer": "延吉"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "牡丹江",
        "answer_ok": ["牡丹江"],
        "display_answer": "牡丹江"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "佳木斯",
        "answer_ok": ["佳木斯"],
        "display_answer": "佳木斯"
    },
    {
        "display_question": "理科",
        "answer_ok": ["理科"],
        "display_answer": "理科"
    }
]